export const QuestionsList = [
    {
      id: 418,
      question: "The individual performing internal quality audit shall be ",
      option_1: "A. Trained in the audit methodology.",
      option_2: "B. Approved by Management Representative",
      option_3: "C. Independent of the function being audited.",
      option_4: "A and C above",
      correct_answer: "A and C above",
    },
    {
      id: 228,
      question:
        "Which engineering inspection method is often used to assess the condition of industrial equipment, such as pumps, motors, and bearings?",
      option_1: "Visual inspection",
      option_2: "Ultrasonic testing",
      option_3: "Radiographic testing",
      option_4: "nan",
      correct_answer: "Ultrasonic testing",
    },
    {
      id: 314,
      question:
        "An internal component used for the separation of solids from flue or product gas in a fluid coking unit is called",
      option_1: "a cyclone",
      option_2: "plenum",
      option_3: "riser of FCU",
      option_4: "none of the above",
      correct_answer: "a cyclone",
    },
    {
      id: 206,
      question: "What is the primary goal of Destructive Testing (DT)?",
      option_1: "To examine materials without causing any damage",
      option_2: "To evaluate the integrity of materials or components",
      option_3: "To intentionally damage materials to assess their properties",
      option_4: "To create destructive materials",
      correct_answer:
        "To intentionally damage materials to assess their properties",
    },
    {
      id: 286,
      question: "Surface discontinuities on nuts are?",
      option_1: "Folds ",
      option_2: "Seams ",
      option_3: "Bursts",
      option_4: "All of the above",
      correct_answer: "All of the above",
    },
    {
      id: 158,
      question:
        "The type of check sheet which specifies the variety of defects with their frequency of occurrence is called _________",
      option_1: "Process distribution check sheet",
      option_2: "Defective item check sheet",
      option_3: "Defect location check sheet",
      option_4: "Defect factor check sheet",
      correct_answer: "Defective item check sheet",
    },
    {
      id: 255,
      question: "When Indian Boiler Regulation came into existence",
      option_1: "1947",
      option_2: "1950",
      option_3: "1923",
      option_4: "1960",
      correct_answer: "1950",
    },
    {
      id: 159,
      question:
        "The type of check sheet which identifies where defects occur in a product is called _______",
      option_1: "Process distribution check sheet",
      option_2: "Defective item check sheet",
      option_3: "Defect location check sheet",
      option_4: "Defect factor check sheet",
      correct_answer: "Defect location check sheet",
    },
    {
      id: 343,
      question: "Osmotic blistering is most likely to occur as a result of  ",
      option_1: "Airless spray application ",
      option_2: "Over coating a surface contaminated with chemical salts ",
      option_3: "Inadequate anchor pattern/surface profile  ",
      option_4: "Applying the coating too thin  ",
      correct_answer: "Over coating a surface contaminated with chemical salts ",
    },
    {
      id: 302,
      question:
        "How much should be the length of the template to measure the shell profile?",
      option_1:
        "To measure the shell profile, template length equal to one quarter of the internal diameter",
      option_2:
        "To measure the shell profile, template length equal to half of the internal diameter",
      option_3:
        "To measure the shell profile, template length equal to one quarter of the external diameter",
      option_4:
        "To measure the shell profile, template length equal to half of the external diameter",
      correct_answer:
        "To measure the shell profile, template length equal to one quarter of the internal diameter",
    },
  ];
  